### Contact

abnertb15@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/abner-misigina (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Microsoft Excel PostgreSQL

Epidemiology

### Languages

English (Full Professional)

### Certifications

Certificate of Completion on Data Analytics

# Abner Misigina

Data Analytics Graduate at Thinkful Oakland

### Summary

I am an aspiring Data Analyst proficient in MS Excel, SQL, Tableau, and Python. I have more than ten years of professional experience in Healthcare data analysis, which has allowed me to develop my Data Analysis and research skills. My goal is to join a Healthcare Data Analytics team.

- Software Skills MS Excel, MS PowerPoint, SQL, Tableau, Python, and SPSS
- Technical Skills Data Exploration, Data Cleaning and Extraction,
  Data Analysis, Data Modeling, Data Visualization, and Data
  Presentation

## Experience

GardaWorld

Security Officer

July 2017 - Present (4 years 1 month)

San Francisco, California, United States

- Conducted security and emergency life safety activities, and followed building post orders and communications.
- Coordinated with the team and communications, provided efficient customer service, and utilized MS Outlook and its calendar, camera systems, and company webpages to execute security activities.

#### FHI 360

**Technical Officer** 

January 2010 - November 2015 (5 years 11 months)

Addis Ababa, Ethiopia

- Executed Healthcare Data Analysis, Monitoring, Evaluation, and Reporting activities
- Conducted surveys developed protocol, pretested, trained, and supervised data collection and data entry, cleaned data and analyzed using SPSS, and prepared report and presentations

## Education

Thinkful

Certificate, Data Analytics · (January 2021 - July 2021)

Jimma University

US Equivalent Bachelor's degree, Epidemiology · (2006 - 2008)

**Debub University** 

Bachelor's degree, Public Health · (1999 - 2003)